Guide to the Yale Dramatic Association Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Phonograph recordings, photographs, programs, and posters, 1900-1993; Accession 1993-A-084
  - Posters
    - Captain Brassbound's Conversion, 1929 (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - The Cherry Orchard, undated (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - Chicago, 1981, undated (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - Cloud Nine, 1990 (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - Cold Sweat, 1992 (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - Cole Porter Revue (auditions), undated (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - Colombe, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - Comedy of Errors, 1938, 1985 (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - The Critic and The Fire Eater, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - Danny and Faye
      See: "A Family of Four" box 1, folder 2
    - Déjà Revue, undated (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - Design for Living, undated (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - The Devil's Disciple, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - Dracula, undated (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - Duchess of Malfi, undated (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - The Eclipse of Lawry, 1992 (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - Edmond, undated (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - Exit to Your Right
      See: "Silly Putty" box 3, folder 8
    - Fiddler on the Roof, undated (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - The Fire Eater
      See "The Critic," box 1A, folder 3.
    - Fruits of Culture, undated (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - The Glass Menagerie, undated (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - Golden Boy, undated (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - The Good Woman of Setzuan, undated (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - Grand Tour, undated (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - Guys and Dolls, 1987 (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - Gypsy, undated (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - Hair, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Hay-Foot Straw-foot, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - He Who Gets Slapped, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Heartbreak Hotel, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - The Hostage, undated (Folder 4)
    - The House of Blue Leaves
      See: "Little Murders" box 2, folder 6
    - How Alex Looks When She's Hurt
    - Il Ventaglio, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - In the Boom Boom Room, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - In the Image of Kings, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Into the Woods, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - J.B., undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - The Jew of Malta, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Kiss Me Kate, 1980, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Knickerbocker Holiday, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - La Ronde, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Ladies in Waiting, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Landscape of the Body, 1989 (Folder 4)
    - Last Indian Summer, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Leonce and Lena, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Let's Do It, undated (Folder 4)
    - Little Murders and The House of Blue Leaves, 1975, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Little Wimmin
    - Love's Labour's Lost, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - The Maids, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Makin' Light (auditions), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Makin' Light, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Marie and Bruce, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Meanwhile, Back at the Castle, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Medea, 1993 (Folder 4)
    - Men Without Shadows, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Merton of the Movies, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Mime, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Mind Games and Poster Child, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Mind the Music, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - The Miracle Worker, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Misalliance, undated (Folder 4)
    - Noises Off, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Of Thee I Sing, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Oh, Kay!, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Old Times, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Once (again) Upon a Mattress, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - The Only Jealousy of Emer
      See: "America Hurrah" box 1, folder 2
    - Our Country's God, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Pantagleize, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Paradise Hotel, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Penumbra, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Peter Pan, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Phèdra, undated (Folder 4)
    - Philoctetes, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Poster Child
      See: "Mind Games" box 2, folder 6
    - Quentin Durward, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - The Rape of Blanche Dubois and The Antimacassar Massacre, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Revizór, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Roman Summer (auditions), undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Romeo and Juliet (auditions), undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Romeo and Juliet, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - The Room, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Sail Away, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Scapino, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - The Second Shepherd's Play, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Sergeant Musgrave's Dance, undated
      See: map case drawer 122
    - Silly Putty and Exit to Your Right, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - So What!, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Starting Here Starting Now, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Stover at Yale, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Suicide in B-Flat, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Sweeney Todd, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - The Tempest, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Tentative Plans, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Three Sisters (director: Bart deLorenzo), undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - The Three Sisters, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Tintypes, 1982 (Folder 4)
    - Tom Jones, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Too Many Boys, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Top Girls, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Trouble in Tahiti, 1980, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - The Truth About Blayds, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Twelfth Night, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - West Side Story (director: Rebecca Guy), undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - West Side Story, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - When You Comin' Back, Red Ryder? (auditions), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - When You Comin' Back, Red Ryder?, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?
      - 1979 (Folder 4)
      - 1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - The Woman, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Zandra's Daughter
    - Organizational meetings, 1950, 1990, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Set Designs
    - Anyone Can Whistle, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Camino Real, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Touch of the Poet, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Production scores, 1938-1962; Accession 1993-A-089
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - So What!, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Tempest, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - We've Got a Lot in Common, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Unidentified, No Date (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Script, score, poster, and program from the Yale Dramatic Association production of Tom Jones, 1960; Accession 1999-A-024
  - Script, score, poster, and program from the Yale Dramatic Association production of Tom Jones, 1960 (Box 1)
- Production notebook, script, videocassettes and audio tape of various productions, 1941, circa 1978-1992; Accession 1999-A-031
  - Production notebook: Gypsy, undated (Box 1)
  - Script and photograph: Hamlet, 1941
  - Memorabilia (t-shirts) (Box 2)
  - Frank Giano, directors tape and description, videotape (VHS) (Box 3)
    Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
  - West Side Story, 1992; videotape (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Twilight and the Fall with discussion, 1989; videotape (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Christopher (Acts I-III), 1978; audiocassette (Box 6)
- President's record notebook, circa 1901-1921; Accession 2000-A-003
  - President's record notebook, circa 1901-1921 (Box 1)
- Posters by Yale Dramat, 1951-1954; Accession 2000-A-029 (Folder 1)
- Posters, photographs, slides and renderings of Yale Dramatic Association productions, 1921-1993; Accession 2000-A-030 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  No inventory available
- Posters, 1992-1996; Accession 2001-A-124 (Folder 1)
- Costume design by Tammy McBride for MacBeth, undated; Accession 2003-A-166
  - Costume design by Tammy McBride for MacBeth, Undated (Box 1)
- Programs and articles about theatrical productions of the Yale Dramatic Association, circa 1940; Accession 2004-A-175 (Box 1)
- Fall Season 2004 materials; Light plots and set plans, 1994-2004; Accession 2005-A-095 (Box 1–3)
- Yale Dramat production photographs, Accession 2006-A-089
  - Unknown production photographs (2) (Box 1)
- Photographic negatives of productions, 1953-1956; Accession 2011-A-004 (Box 1)